Ghayeth Al Masri

J +963 932 482 089

linkedin.com/in/ghayeth-al-masri-a13704241/ —

portfolio portfolio

Objective:

I am a Computer Engineer with over a year of experience in back-end development, building efficient, scalable and maintainable applications. I have worked with Java (Spring), Go (Fiber) and PHP (Laravel) on independent and team-based projects.

Experience

Backend Developer - Internship

Karabük Üniversitesi Demir Çelik Enstitüsü Karabük Üniversitesi Demir Çelik Enstitüsü Feb 2024 - May 2024 Jul 2024 - Jul 2024

- Web: Go, Fiber (HTTP Framework), SSR (Server-Side Rendering), RESTful API, JSON.
- Production: Docker.
- Databases: MySQL (RDS), Redis (NoSQL).
- Others: Agile Kanban, Git/GitHub, Unit testing, SOLID, Design Patterns.

Project (Labsis):

- Description:

Labsis system is an automation platform for managing laboratories, viewing test prices, generating proformas, submitting applications, and tracking results. Designed for researchers, engineers, and industry professionals.

- Role:
 - Feb May 2024: Establishing core services for Labsis.
 - Jul Jul 2024: Enhancing user experience, monitoring the deployed system.

Java Swing - Internship Aug 2022 - Sep 2022

Karabük Üniversitesi Bilgi İşlem Başkanlığı

- Java: Java 8, Composition, Exception Handling, Collection Framework.
- **Swing**: JFrame, JPanel, GridLayout.
- RDS&Data Access: MySQL, JDBC.

Project (CRUD-App):

- Description:

A school system for managing courses, students, tutors.

Projects

Check out my portfolio for more details about the projects. (Portfolio - Ghayeth)

Education

Karabuk University

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

2019 - 2024

Skills

Languages: Java, Go, C, HTML.

Frameworks: Spring (Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring MVC), Fiber, Laravel.

Databases: MySQL, SQL, Redis **Tools**: Postman, GitHub, Docker. **Methodologies**: Agile Kanban.

Testing: Unit testing, Integration testing.

Others: SOLID, OOP, Design Patterns, Clean Architecture, RESTful API, Database design.

Some experience: JavaScript.

2040 2024

Arabic English Turkish